!function(){"use strict";function e(e){e.otherwise("/")}angular.module("quizApp",["ngRoute","ngAnimate","ngMaterial"]).config(e),e.$inject=["$routeProvider"]}(),function(){"use strict";function e(e){function t(){$("html, body").animate({scrollTop:$(document).height()},1e3)}var o=this;o.submitted=!1,o.letters=["A","B","C","D","E","F"],o.correctAnswers=0,o.questions=[{question:"What shape do hereditary spherocyte RBCs have?",correct:!0,answers:[{text:"Bi-concave"},{text:"Triangular"},{text:"Spherical",correct:!0},{text:"Pyramidal"},{text:"Quadrangular"}]},{question:"The most common cause of hereditary spherocytosis is due to:",correct:!0,answers:[{text:"Autosomal Recessive"},{text:"Autosomal Dominant",correct:!0},{text:"X-linked Recessive"},{text:"X-linked Dominant"},{text:"Spontaneous Mutation"}]},{question:"What is a diagnostic test used for hereditary spherocytosis?",correct:!0,answers:[{text:"Western blot with PCR"},{text:"A1C test"},{text:"Chest x-ray"},{text:"Reticulocyte count",correct:!0},{text:"Echocardiogram"}]},{question:"What are some signs/symptoms of hereditary spherocytosis?",correct:!0,answers:[{text:"Anemia, jaundice, splenomegaly, gall stones",correct:!0},{text:"Anemia, ulcers, jaundice, gall stones"},{text:"Splenomegaly, hepatomegaly, jaundice, ulcers"},{text:"Jaundice, gall stones, hepatomegaly, anemia"},{text:"Splenomegaly, ulcers, anemia, gall stones"}]},{question:"Some treatments used for hereditary spherocytosis are:",correct:!0,answers:[{text:"Folic acid, iron, splenectomy"},{text:"Splenectomy, anticoagulants, folic acid"},{text:"Folic acid, cholecystectomy, splenectomy",correct:!0},{text:"Folic acid, phototherapy, hepatectomy"},{text:"Iron, anticoagulants, folic acid"}]},{question:"Where is the defective rbc undergoing hemolysis?",correct:!0,answers:[{text:"In the bone marrow as the reticulocyte is being formed"},{text:"In the capillaries, because the shape is not flexible and the rbc becomes lodged",correct:!0},{text:"In the alveoli of the lungs because it doesn’t carry enough hemoglobin for gas exchange"},{text:"in the liver sinusoids by Kupffer cells"}]},{question:"How does the aplastic crisis arise?",correct:!0,answers:[{text:"As the immature red blood cell is released into the circulation"},{text:"When the spleen has destroyed enough red blood cells to create anemia"},{text:"After the hematopoietic cells of the bone marrow reach their full capacity to regenerate reticulocytes and still cannot maintain homeostasis",correct:!0},{text:"Because the liver is destroying red blood cells faster than they can be produced"}]},{question:"Where is the megaloblastic crisis occurring?",correct:!0,answers:[{text:"In the liver sinusoids, where rbc’s are being destroyed and causing hepatomegaly"},{text:"In the hematopoietic cells of the bone marrow"},{text:"In the yellow bone marrow"},{text:"In the sinusoids of the spleen, causing splenomegaly due to chronic inflammation secondary to the increased rate of rbc destruction",correct:!0}]},{question:"What forms the gallstones seen in Moderate to Severe Spherocytosis?",correct:!0,answers:[{text:"High levels of bilirubin in the peripheral blood due to red blood cell hemolysis",correct:!0},{text:"High blood levels of calcium secondary to red blood cell hemolysis"},{text:"High blood levels of free hemoglobin released from lysed red blood cells"},{text:"The spleen releasing large amounts of phospholipids derived from destroyed red blood cell membranes"}]},{question:"How is bone marrow function assessed?",correct:!0,answers:[{text:"By ordering a complete blood cell count (CBC)"},{text:"With a lymphocyte and platelet count"},{text:"With a reticulocyte count to look for immature red blood cells",correct:!0},{text:"By drawing a bone marrow sample from the pelvis"}]}],o.showPercent=function(){var e=o.correctAnswers/o.questions.length*100;return parseInt(e)+"%"},o.refresh=function(){e.location.reload()},o.submit=function(){o.quizForm.$invalid||(o.submitted=!0,o.correctAnswers=0,o.questions.forEach(function(e){e.answers[e.selected].correct===!0?(e.correct=!0,o.correctAnswers+=1):e.correct=!1}),t())}}angular.module("quizApp").controller("HomeController",e),e.$inject=["$window"]}();